

Tomáš Javorský

About Me

I'm an IT developer focused on front end web development in React and Node.js ecosystem. In the past, I have worked in different IT fields, ranging from game development in Unity, trough mobile application in native Android all the way to front end development in React. I have received a Master's degree in Computer Science, however, most of my skills are self taught. I am a fast learner and my proficiency in various programming fields together with skill in 2D and 3D graphical software makes me a very versatile asset to any team.

Education

Master's degree in Service Science, Management, and Engineering Faculty of Informatics Masaryk University - 2018 Thesis: Body Transfer Illusion in VR - https://is.muni.cz/th/y73cq/

Experience

React Developer at K2NG

Coding Front-end web e-mobility tools in React for Skoda. 2021 - 2022 - skoda-auto.com

React Developer at COD8

Coding various Front-end web applications in React and mobile apps in React Native. 2020 - 2021 - cod8.io/.

React Developer at Shipmonk

Coding front-end of fulfillment management web application in React, with Redux and Material UI. 2020 - 2020 - shipmonk.com

React Developer at QEST

2019 - 2020 - quest.cz

React + Node.js Developer

Unity Dev at Powerplay Studio

2017 - 2019 - powerplay.studio

Android Dev at Reinto

2016 - 2017 - reinto.cz

3D artist & Unity Dev at iMax Games

2015 - 2016 - facebook.com/imaxgames/

Skills



React **React Native**

























English





Volunteering

Erasmus Student Network

Masaryk University - 2015 - 2017

Preservation of environment

Workcamps by IJGD, SIW and NICE Hann. Münden - Germany - 2006 Ameland - Holland - 2007 Gevelsberg - Germany - 2008 Shiiba - Japan - 2014

Links



tomasjavorsky.github.io



linkedin.com/in/tomasjavorsky

Contact Me



tomus.dev@gmail.com



Prague, Czech Republic

